Persico, Joseph; Papers apap030
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1960-2002; 4; 1 cubic foot
  - Bernard Geis Associates, Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Publications, Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 46 (4-Correspondence), Folder 19)
- Biographical, 1958-2001; 5; 0.17 cubic ft. 2 films
  The Biographical series is predominantly material from early in Persico's career. Included are folders related to his election as the Executive Secretary of the New York State Young Democrats in 1958 and his time as a Foreign Service Officer in Latin America. Of particular biographical note are the scrapbook and news clippings folders which include selected highlights from throughout Persico's career in government service and as an author.
  - Latin America, ca. 1959-1962 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 1)
  - Letter to the Editor, Anonymous, 1963 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 2)
  - Persico, News Clippings, 1975-2001 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 3)
  - Resume, 1966 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 4)
  - Saint Rose Cup Polo Match, Scholarship, 1997 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, ca. 1959-1990 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 6)
  - Young Democrats, 1958 (Box 47 (5-Biographical), Folder 7)
  - "The Naked Writer" Lecture for the New York State Writers Institute, University at Albany, Page Hall, Master and Use Copies, VHS, 2001 March 14 (Box 47 (5-Biographical))